- ̗̀( 📞˶'ᵕ'˶) ̖́-　･*:.｡ ｡.:*･ﾟHello?✽.｡.:*
No news is good news
Antarctic "Shirase" is good luck
Neither here nor there, stuck in a rut
My niche feelings are all scattered around
Total obsession, my little cosmos
Now transmitting, a CHU for you
Wandering around, oh my dear lord
ｍosi-mosi? Can you hear me?
Signals, signals, mysterious signals
Head over heels, transmitting through space
Hop-step-jump for a thousand meters
Even if cats hate me, even if Mom scolds me
I'll meet you, the one who's just right for me
✽.｡.: Sorry, she's on the phone right now... *･ﾟ
CQCQ, where are you, alien?
Sob-sob, such a lonely area
Wo ai ni, Hello, How are you?
Love and Peace, we're on the same wavelength
How many light-years from my house to there?
Or is it just next door in the 3rd Block?
Where did my abducted heart go?
In a ***QLO down jacket, is space cold?
But still, I can't find you anywhere
My gray feelings are hanging in mid-air
I'm gonna find you, UFO!
And tell you how much I've wanted to see you
Signals, signals... ah, out of service
Still, head over heels, transmitting away
Something's weird, Mr. Invader
This love I pour only into you
Signals, signals, mysterious signals
Head over heels, transmitting through space
Something's weird, Mr. Invader
This love I dedicate only to you, Ah
Signals, signals, red signals
Wrapped in a ribbon, now sending it out
Signals, signals, can you hear me?
Even if my heart is snatched away
Right now, I will meet you
The one for me
My one and only
4season
I miss you
Love-dense
Thank you for listening:))